<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">SmartCampus</string>
    <string name="bold" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/latobold</string>
    <string name="regular" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/latoregular</string>
    <string name="light" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/latolight</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="save_button">Save_post</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="about_university">
        Being established in 2002, it has become a
        prominent private university in Bangladesh. Our 150
        Acre campus is full of life and positive energy,
        fostering education and innovation for more than 20000 students.
    </string>
    <string name="fragment_about">
Daffodil International University was established on 24 January 2002.
It follows a liberal arts approach to education which nurtures fresh
        ideas and gives new impetus to the field of tertiary education.
It ensures a high quality of education and aims to meet the demands of contemporary times.Building on
        Dius experience of seeking solutions to challenges posed by extreme poverty.
Diu hopes to instill in its students a commitment to working towards national development and progress. Diu is accredited by the University Grants Commission (UGC) and approved by the Ministry of education, Government of Bangladesh.\n
\n

Mission :

The mission of Daffodil International University is to foster the national development process through the creation of a center of excellence in higher education that is responsive to society\'s needs, and able to develop and create leaders.
It actively contributes to learning and the creation of knowledge.\n
\n
        Goal:

The goal of the university is to provide an excellent broad-based education with a focus on professional development for students, in order to equip them with the knowledge and skills necessary for leading the country in its quest for development.
Along with this, the university provides an environment for faculty development to ensure a dynamic teaching environment. faculty will be provided with an environment in which they can further their teaching-learning abilities and contribute to the creation of new knowledge by developing and using their research skills.
    </string>

    <string-array name="theme">
        <item>System Default</item>
        <item>Dark</item>
        <item>Light</item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>